# **ZHAN RUI YAP (RAY)**

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Master qualified graduate offering software development and part-time work experience with extensive knowledge of core subject matter. Detail-oriented with excellent observational, organizational and communication skills. Hardworking and willing to actively learn and take on responsibility to meet team goals.

### WORK HISTORY

# Software Developer Intern, 02/2024 to 06/2024 Inflamed Pty Ltd – Melbourne, VIC

- Developed software components using Next.js, React and cloud computing technologies such as Google Cloud.
- Gained experience in health/medical IT field.
- Engaged in continuous learning and feedback sessions, focusing on soft skills development and embracing new methodologies.
- Implemented SMART on FHIR which is a data standard that enables applications to access information in electronic health record (EHR) systems.
- Increased skills in integrating APIs for data retrieval and communication, enhancing software functionality and facilitating seamless interaction between different system components.

## Food Court Attendant, 02/2023 to 02/2024 Rhumbas@Crown Casino - Southbank, VIC

- Enhanced customer satisfaction by providing efficient and friendly service in a fast-paced environment.
- Maintained high food quality standards by following proper food handling and storage procedures.
- Contributed to increased sales through upselling menu items and promoting special offers.
- Ensured a clean and welcoming atmosphere for guests by regularly sanitizing surfaces and equipment.
- Expedited orders accurately, ensuring timely delivery of meals to customers.

### Floor Staff Member, 08/2020 to 12/2021 Century Pharmacy - Malaysia

- Increased efficiency in floor operations by organizing and stocking merchandise, reducing clutter and ensuring optimal product placement.
- Assisted customers with inquiries, locating products, and making informed recommendations to meet their needs.
- Collaborated with team members to maintain store appearance, resulting in a more enjoyable shopping experience for customers.

### CONTACT

**Location:** Melbourne **Phone:** +61-452370822

Email: vapzhanrui@outlook.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zryy/

### SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python |
  Java | C# | JavaScript | Objective C |
  C++ | HTML | CSS | Next.js | React
- Soft Skills: Teamwork/Collaboration, Communication, Technical Writing, Presentations, Debugging, Research
- Databases: Database Designing, SQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Google Cloud
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux
- Languages: English, Mandarin, Cantonese, Malay
- Other qualities: Active listening, Attention to detail, Conflict resolution, Time management

#### **EDUCATION**

### Master of Information Technology, Cybersecurity, 2023-2024 University of Melbourne - Parkville, VIC

- Focus areas on Web security, Security analytics and Fundamentals of cybersecurity, Risk management and Team Projects & Collaboration
- Weighted Average Mark 72

# **Bachelor of Computer Science, Advanced Computer Science, 2020-2022 Monash University** - Clayton, VIC

- Specialised in Advanced Computer Science
- Focused on algorithms and learning, problem solving and exposure to different fields in computer science and technology.
- Weighted Average Mark 75.00

# **PROJECTS**

# Augmented Reality Temporal Bone Surgery Simulator (Feb 2024 – June 2024)

### **University of Melbourne Software Project**

- Collaborated with a team of university students and external clients.
- Migration of outdated 3D surgery simulator to a new AR environment.
- Development experience in Unity including C# and C++.
- Led the development and implementation of the user interface (UI) for the simulator.
- Applied the marching cubes algorithm to render detailed and accurate bone models for the AR environment.

### Suggestion Website (Oct 2022 - Jan 2023)

**Personal Project**, https://github.com/yapzhanrui2/SuggestionApp

- Built a website application to allows users to provide suggestions for a specific platform/topic with C# and .NET 6.0 framework (Blazor Server)
- Created database using MongoDB (Mainly implementing mongoDB Atlas cloud database)
- Managed user authentication and authorisation with Azure Active Directory B2C
- Implemented both desktop and mobile layouts for website to accommodate different platforms.

# Dish Recommender App (Feb 2022 - Nov 2022) Monash University, Team Project

- Collaborated in a team of four for bachelor's degree final year project.
- Built an android application designed to recommend dishes to users based on dietary requirements and taste preferences, recommendations done through SQL queries.
- Managed frontend written in Java using Android Studio and backend using Go with MongoDB and mySQL.
- Created account login system and allows recommendation for nearby restaurants based on user's location.

### EXTRACURRICULAR

## Volunteer for orientation activities, 02/2023 University of Melbourne

- Assisted in organising and executing orientation events for new students, ensuring a smooth transition into university life.
- Facilitated ice-breaking activities and group sessions to help new students build connections.
- Guided group of new students around faculty and campus.

## Volunteer for Peer Mentoring, 03/2019 – 11/2019 Sunway College

- Achieved excellent marks in Mathematics and Economics, leading to selection as a peer mentor.
- Conducted weekly mentoring sessions, guiding students through worksheets and problem sets provided by professors.
- Developed strong communication and teaching skills by tailoring explanations to individual learning styles.

### President of Computer Science Club, 02/2016 – 11/2018 Poi Lam High School, Malaysia

- Organised and led a welcoming party for new members at the beginning of each academic year, fostering a sense of community.
- Conducted weekly learning activities, including workshops on new tools and basic programming, enhancing members' technical skills.
- Developed leadership and organisational skills by managing club operations and facilitating collaborative projects.

#### REFEREES

### Mari Robert

### **Founder & CEO of Inflamed**

Email: mari@inflamed.com.au

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/marirobert/

Phone: Available on request

Jeffrey Lo

Manager, Rhumbas Crown

Phone: 04-52184324